We found Zheng Sheng's death notice.
تم العثور على إشعار وفاة تشنغ شنغ.
This tailor is really thorough in his actions.
هذا الخياط يقوم بعمله بشكل مثالي حقًا.
It seems he's planning to kill everyone responsible for Zhao Ping'an's death.
يبدو أنه يريد قتل كل من تسبب في موت تشاو بينغ آن.
Go investigate Zheng Sheng's house immediately.
اذهب الآن على الفور للتحقيق في منزل تشنغ شنغ.
Alright, alright.
حسنًا، حسنًا.
we'll go investigate Zheng Sheng's situation right away.
سنذهب الآن للتحقيق في وضع تشنغ شنغ.
Okay.
حسنًا.
I'll call you when we have results.
سأتصل بكم عندما تكون هناك نتائج.
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
It's confirmed that Zheng Sheng has also been kidnapped.
تم التأكد من أن تشنغ شنغ قد تم اختطافه أيضًا.
Let's go to Zheng Sheng's house to gather more information.
دعونا نذهب إلى منزل تشنغ شنغ لمعرفة الوضع.
Let's go.
هيا.
Zheng Sheng hasn't been found yet.
لم نعثر على تشنغ شنغ بعد.
Why are we going back to De City?
لماذا نعود إلى مدينة دي؟
Because Zheng Sheng is very likely in De City right now.
لأن تشنغ شنغ من المحتمل جدًا أن يكون في مدينة دي الآن.
You've figured out the meaning of that sentence?
هل فهمت معنى هذه الجملة؟
Although there's only one possibility,
رغم أن هناك احتمال واحد فقط،
it can only be this way.
لكن هذا هو الاحتمال الوحيد.
It ends at the beginning.
النهاية في البداية.
If it's the tailor,
إذا كان الخياط،
this sentence must have some cause and effect relationship.
فلابد أن هذه الجملة لها علاقة سببية.
As for the ending,
إذا كانت النهاية،
it should refer to when Zhao Ping'an was officially killed.
فيجب أن تشير إلى مقتل تشاو بينغ آن رسميًا.
The beginning should be when Zheng Sheng decided to develop the land
والبداية يجب أن تكون قرار تشنغ شنغ بتطوير الأرض
and build Xinxin Department Store.
وبناء متجر شينشين.
If that's the case,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
Zheng Sheng is very likely
فمن المحتمل جدًا
somewhere in Xinxin Department Store.
أن يكون تشنغ شنغ في مكان ما في متجر شينشين.
And the time of death
وأيضًا وقت الوفاة
should be the same as Zhao Ping'an's death time,
يجب أن يكون نفس وقت وفاة تشاو بينغ آن،
which is 10 PM.
أي الساعة العاشرة مساءً.
10 PM?
الساعة العاشرة مساءً.
This tailor seems to have quite a sense of ceremony in his actions.
إذن، هذا الخياط لديه إحساس بالطقوس في أفعاله.
Alright then.
حسنًا.
I'll go make arrangements.
سأذهب لأرتب الأمر.
Let's depart right away.
سننطلق على الفور.
Let's go.
هيا.
What should we do now?
ماذا نفعل الآن؟
We've searched everywhere in Zheng Sheng's house and Shengfeng Money House.
لقد بحثنا في كل مكان في منزل تشنغ شنغ ومصرف شنغ فنغ.
We didn't find anything valuable.
لم نجد أي شيء ذي قيمة.
Oh, right.
آه، صحيح.
Why are we coming to Xinxin Department Store?
لماذا أتينا إلى متجر شين شين؟
Are you going shopping?
هل تريد شراء شيء ما؟
Xinxin Department Store is the initial connection point
متجر شين شين هو نقطة الاتصال الأولى
between Zheng Sheng and Zhao Ping'an.
بين تشنغ شنغ وتشاو بينغ آن.
It's also the beginning of Zhao Ping'an's tragic life.
إنها أيضًا بداية حياة تشاو بينغ آن المأساوية.
Perhaps we can find some unexpected gains.
ربما نجد شيئًا غير متوقع.
That makes sense.
هذا منطقي.
Let's go in and take a look.
دعنا ندخل ونلقي نظرة.
Let's go.
هيا.
Hey.
هي.
What are you two sneaking around for?
ماذا تفعلون هنا بهذه الطريقة المريبة؟
Who are you calling sneaky?
من تقصد بالمريب؟
Oh.
أوه.
So it's the two bosses.
إنهما المديران.
I apologize for not recognizing you.
أعتذر عن عدم التعرف عليكما.
May I ask what brings you here?
هل يمكنني أن أعرف سبب زيارتكما؟
Where's your manager?
أين مديركم؟
We need to see him.
نحتاج إلى التحدث معه.
The manager?
المدير؟
Just turn this corner.
إنه هناك، بعد المنعطف.
Do you need me to accompany you?
هل تريدون مني مرافقتكم؟
No need, we can go by ourselves.
لا، شكرًا. يمكننا الذهاب بأنفسنا.
Alright, got it.
حسنًا، جيد.
Don't come any closer.
لا تقترب.
You must be Song Si, right?
أنت سونغ سي، أليس كذلك؟
How do you know?
كيف عرفت ذلك؟
Of course I know.
بالطبع أعرف.
Although you're not as clever as Gong Sun He,
على الرغم من أنك لست ذكيًا مثل غونغسون هه،
I know that
لكنني أعرف
your forensic skills are excellent.
أن مستواك في الطب الشرعي عالٍ جدًا.
Are you interested
هل لديك اهتمام
in joining us?
بالانضمام إلينا؟
You want me, a forensic expert,
أنت تريد مني، كطبيب شرعي،
to join your criminal gang?
أن أنضم إلى عصابتكم الإجرامية غير القانونية.
You must be dreaming.
أنت تحلم.
Let me ask you,
دعني أسألك،
aren't Zheng Sheng and Lin Li
تشنغ شنغ ولين لي
breaking the law by conspiring to harm Zhao Ping'an?
ألم يرتكبا جريمة عندما تآمرا معًا لإيذاء تشاو بينغ آن؟
Zhou Xiaokang's violent debt collection from Zhao Ping'an,
تشو شياو كانغ يستخدم العنف لتحصيل الديون من تشاو بينغ آن،
making him and his family live in fear every day,
مما يجعله وعائلته يعيشون في خوف كل يوم.
isn't that a crime?
أليس هذا جريمة؟
When the victims really need you,
عندما يحتاج الضحايا إليكم حقًا،
where are you?
أين أنتم؟
Zhao Ping'an didn't report it to the police. If he had,
تشاو بينغ آن لم يبلغ الشرطة. إذا أبلغ الشرطة،
Even if he had reported it,
حتى لو تم الإبلاغ،
the matter would have been dismissed.
فإن هذه القضية ستنتهي دون نتيجة.
Because Zhao Ping'an
لأن تشاو بينغ آن
is just a nobody.
مجرد شخص صغير،
Your police station wouldn't risk offending
وقسم الشرطة لن يغضب رجل أعمال كبير مثل تشنغ شنغ
a business tycoon like Zheng Sheng for a nobody.
من أجل شخص صغير.
You really underestimate our police station.
إذن فأنت تستخف حقًا بقسم الشرطة لدينا.
We don't fear the rich and powerful.
قسم الشرطة لدينا لا يخاف من أصحاب النفوذ.
If you're just talking about yourself, I believe you.
إذا كنت تتحدث عن نفسك فقط، فأنا أصدقك.
But your police station...
لكن قسم الشرطة الخاص بكم...
Alright,
حسنًا،
I won't waste any more words with you.
لن أضيع المزيد من الوقت معك.
If you want to save them,
إذا كنت تريد إنقاذهم،
it's impossible.
فهذا مستحيل.
They have bombs strapped to them.
لقد تم ربط قنابل بأجسادهم.
If you don't want me to blow up the entire mall,
إذا كنت لا تريدني أن أفجر المركز التجاري بأكمله،
I suggest you evacuate everyone immediately.
فأنصحك بإخلاء الناس بسرعة.
Also,
وأيضًا،
give Gong Sun He a message.
أوصل رسالة إلى غونغسون هه.
Tell him to come up alone.
قل له أن يأتي وحده.
I'll be waiting for him here.
سأنتظره هنا.
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
Get out of here quickly.
اخرجوا من هنا بسرعة.
There's danger upstairs.
هناك خطر في الطابق العلوي.
Everyone, leave this place.
اخرجوا جميعا من هنا.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
بسرعة، بسرعة، بسرعة.
You've finally arrived.
لقد وصلتم أخيرا.
Zheng Sheng is upstairs, and there's a bomb up there too.
تشنغ شنغ في الأعلى، وهناك قنبلة أيضا.
Quickly arrange for people to evacuate the crowd.
رتبوا بسرعة لإخلاء الحشد.
Alright.
حسنا.
Evacuate the crowd immediately.
أخلوا الحشد بسرعة.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry!
بسرعة، بسرعة، بسرعة، بسرعة.
What's the situation here?
ما الوضع هنا؟
A man and a woman.
رجل وامرأة.
The man is definitely Zheng Sheng.
الرجل بالتأكيد هو تشنغ شنغ.
We don't know the situation with the woman.
لا نعرف وضع المرأة.
And there are kidnappers too.
وهناك أيضًا خاطفون.
What?
ماذا؟
The Tailor is here too?
الخياط هنا أيضًا.
Yes.
نعم.
What exactly does he want to do?
ماذا يريد أن يفعل بالضبط؟
We were held at gunpoint as soon as we went in.
بمجرد دخولنا، تم توجيه المسدسات إلينا.
And the two hostages both have bombs strapped to them.
والشخصان المختطفان لديهما قنابل على جسديهما.
The kidnapper specifically asked to see you.
الخاطفون طلبوا مقابلتك بالاسم.
It looks like he wants to recruit you.
يبدو أنهم يريدون إشراكك.
This madman.
هذا المجنون.
Then I'll go up and take a look.
سأذهب إلى الأعلى لألقي نظرة.
Hey.
آه.
He said...
قال.
Only Gong Sun He can go up alone.
يمكن لـ قونغ سون هه فقط الصعود.
if they find anyone else upstairs,
إذا تم اكتشاف أي شخص آخر في الطابق العلوي،
he'll detonate the bombs immediately.
سيفجر القنبلة على الفور.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
They're after me.
إنهم يستهدفونني.
I'll definitely bring them back.
سأعيد الأشخاص بالتأكيد.
You must be careful.
يجب أن تنتبه لسلامتك.
Gong Sun He,
قونغ سون هه.
come back safely, okay?
عد بسلام.
Inspector.
المفتش.
Please save me.
أنقذني من فضلك.
Shut up.
اصمت.
I'll blow your head off if you speak again.
إذا تكلمت مرة أخرى سأطلق النار عليك.
Tailor.
الخياط.
You again.
أنت مرة أخرى.
What exactly do you want?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل بالضبط؟
I need you
أحتاج إليك.
to make a choice.
اتخذ قرارا.
I'm the one you're looking for.
أنا الشخص الذي تبحث عنه.
Let them go.
أطلق سراحهم.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
The man is Zheng Sheng.
الرجل هو تشنغ شنغ.
The woman is his wife.
والمرأة هي زوجته.
They're strapped with a special bomb I made.
لقد ربطت بهما قنبلة خاصة صنعتها بنفسي.
If one of them dies,
إذا مات أحدهما فقط،
the bomb will be deactivated.
فستلغى القنبلة.
If they're both alive after ten minutes,
إذا بقي كلاهما على قيد الحياة بعد عشر دقائق،
the bomb will explode.
فستنفجر القنبلة.
If you cut the wrong wire, the bomb will also explode.
إذا قطعت الأسلاك بشكل عشوائي، ستنفجر القنبلة أيضا.
If you were to choose,
إذا كان عليك أن تختار،
which one would you let live?
فمن ستختار للبقاء على قيد الحياة؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تعني؟
It's simple.
إنه بسيط جدا.
You just need to kill one of them,
عليك فقط أن تقتل أحدهما،
and the other will be saved.
وسينجو الآخر.
Now,
الآن،
the choice is yours.
القرار لك.
Let's see what you'll do next.
دعنا نرى ما ستفعله.
Until we meet again.
إلى اللقاء.
Oh, right.
بالمناسبة،
I forgot to tell you.
نسيت أن أخبرك
If I die,
إذا مت
my partners will detonate the other bombs.
سيفجر رفاقي القنابل الأخرى
When that happens, the death toll
في ذلك الوقت، الذين سيموتون
won't be limited to just those two.
لن يكونوا هما الاثنين فقط
Why haven't they shown up yet?
لماذا لم يظهر بعد؟
Th-th-this...
هذا... هذا... هذا...
What's going on here?
ما الذي يحدث هنا؟
We can't just sit here waiting.
لا يمكننا أن نبقى ننتظر هكذا فقط
The tailor has finally shown up.
أخيرًا ظهر هذا الخياط.
If we don't catch him this time,
إذا لم نمسك به هذه المرة،
we might never get another chance.
فلن تكون لدينا فرصة أخرى.
Hey, you guys go block the back door.
هيا، اذهبوا أنتم وسدوا الباب الخلفي.
Zheng Sheng, you won't die a good death!
تشنغ شنغ، لن تموت ميتة طيبة!
You've done bad things and now you're dragging me into it.
لقد ارتكبت أعمالًا سيئة وما زلت تحاول جري معك.
Inspector, I can't die.
سيدي المحقق، لا يمكنني أن أموت.
I have children to take care of.
لدي أطفال.
You can go ahead and die.
يمكنك أن تموت.
I'll raise the children.
سأربي أطفالك.
Inspector Gong Sun,
المحقق غونغسون،
you know who I am, don't you?
أتعرف من أنا، أليس كذلك؟
I'm the owner of Shengfeng Money House.
أنا صاحب مصرف شنغ فنغ.
I'm rich.
أنا غني.
I have lots and lots of money.
لدي الكثير والكثير من المال.
if you can save me,
إذا استطعت إنقاذي.
I can give you 100,000.
يمكنني أن أعطيك مائة ألف.
No, no, no. I'll give you a million silver dollars.
لا لا لا، سأعطيك مليون يوان.
Shut up.
اصمت.
You even killed your wife just to save your own skin.
قتلت حتى زوجتك من أجل البقاء على قيد الحياة.
Can you even be considered human?
هل ما زلت تعتبر نفسك إنسانا؟
You're right. He's not human.
هذا صحيح، إنه ليس إنسانا.
Zheng Sheng, this is your retribution.
تشنغ شنغ، هذا هو جزاؤك.
Detective, Detective, save me!
المفتش، المفتش، أنقذني.
I can't.
لا أستطيع.
Only five minutes left.
بقي خمس دقائق فقط.
I can't disarm it.
لا أستطيع فكها.